Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1973 - 2009
  - Project Space II: Joyce Kim, January 27, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Really: Frank Benson, Steven Brower, David Henry Brown Jr., Alain Bublex, The Butterflies of Love, Kate Howard, Janice Kerbel, Cees Krijnen, Matthieu Laurette, January 27, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Really: Administrative, Artists' Resumes [1 of 2], January 27, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Really: Administrative, Artists' Resumes [2 of 2], January 27, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Really: Financial, Promotional, Research, January 27, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Architecture Design Project Series: A Retroactive Master Plan for Silicon Valley, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Emerging Curator Series: Rigo 01, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Salon: Administrative, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Salon: Alexis Karl, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Salon: Bertrand LaMarche, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Salon: Correspondence, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Salon: Denise Fasanello, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Salon: Giles Lyon, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Salon: Jean-Francois Fourtou, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Salon: Nazareth Pacheco, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Salon: Ursula Hodel, March 31, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Our Perceptions/Urban Reality, May 24, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - "Pictures" at an Exhibition: Administrative, Financial, Promotional, May 24, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - "Pictures" at an Exhibition: De-Installation, May 24, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - "Pictures" at an Exhibition: Loan Agreement Forms, May 24, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - "Pictures" at an Exhibition: Research, May 24, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - "Pictures" at an Exhibition: Santiago Cucullu, May 24, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Schmuck for a Lifetime: Adam Ames, May 24, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Museum of the Ordinary, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Incognito: Mario Alos, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Purloined: Administrative, Promotional, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Purloined: Christine Y. Kim, Curator, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Purloined: Eric Wesley, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Purloined: Guy Overfelt, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Purloined: Lilan Freedland, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Purloined: Lisa E. Levy, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Purloined: Mark Wallinger, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Purloined: Nancy Hwang, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Purloined: Nikki S. Lee, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Sophie Calle, September 6, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Daniel Roth, October 25, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Urban Pornography: Administrative, Catalogue Text, October 25, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Urban Pornography: Administrative, De-Installation, October 25, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Urban Pornography: Administrative, Financial, October 25, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Urban Pornography: Administrative, Research, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Urban Pornography: Administrative, Research, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Urban Pornography: Alex Slade, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Urban Pornography: Artists' Materials [1 of 3], October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Urban Pornography: Artists' Materials [2 of 3], October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Urban Pornography: Artists' Materials [3 of 3], October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Urban Pornography: Bill Owens, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Urban Pornography: Catherine Opie, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Urban Pornography: Doreen Morrissey, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Urban Pornography: Doug Aitken, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Urban Pornography: Edward Ruscha, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Urban Pornography: Exhibition Checklist, Promotional, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Urban Pornography: Francesco Jodice, October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Urban Pornography: Hong Hao, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Urban Pornography: Jean-Luc Moulene, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Urban Pornography: Jonah Freeman [Project Space], October 25, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Urban Pornography: Jordi Bernado, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Urban Pornography: Kevin Landers, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Urban Pornography: Laura Carton, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Urban Pornography: Lisa Roy, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Urban Pornography: Listings, Press Clippings, October 25, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Urban Pornography: Lourdes Grobet, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Urban Pornography: Michael Phelan, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Urban Pornography: Naoya Hatakeyama, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Urban Pornography: Oliver Boberg, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Urban Pornography: Paul Morris Gallery, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Urban Pornography: Shipping, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Urban Pornography: Todd Hido, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Urban Pornography: Warren Neidich [1 of 2], 2001 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Urban Pornography: Warren Neidich [2 of 2], 2001 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Urban Pornography: William Jones, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - A Place Called Oxmoor: Francis Gomila, January 12, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Administrative, Promotional, January 12, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Administrative, Promotional, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Coco Fusco, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Melissa Gould, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Context and Conceptualism: Siemon Allen, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Panic Magic/Crisis Circus: Mayumi Kimura, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Point of View (Dog-Cam Project): Nobuhira Narumi, January 12, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Another Country: John Timberlake, March 14, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Administrative, Promotional, March 21, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Carl Scholz, March 21, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Chris Heenan, March 21, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Demonclownmonkey: David Altmejd, March 21, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Emily Richardson, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Karen Leo, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Michael Byron, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Nayia Frangouli, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Paul G. Wagner, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Demonclownmonkey: Scott Grodesky, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Freecell: Architecture and Design Project Series, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Graft: The Controlled Space, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Love Me Tender: Didier Fiuza Faustino, March 21, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Infotecture, May 30, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Infotecture, May 30, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Parabiosis: Kendall Buster, May 30, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Wunderkammer: A Cabinet of Words - Architecture and Design Project Series featuring Ayse Birsel and Karin Fong, May 30, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Documents: Touhami Ennadre, September 5, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Documents: Touhami Ennadre - Images, September 5, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Meatspace: Architecture and Design Project Series by Lindy Roy, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Multitude: Administrative, Financial, Promotional, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Multitude: Administrative, Financial, Promotional, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Multitude: Ararat Sarkissian, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Multitude: Cari L. Gonzalez-Casanova, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Multitude: Corine Borgnet, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Multitude: Do-Ho Suh, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Multitude: Hong Hao, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Multitude: Installation, Shipping Invoices, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Multitude: Jean Shin, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Multitude: Kamrooz Aram, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Multitude: Nayia Frangouli, September 5, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Multitude: Orit Raff, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Multitude: Rick Buckley, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Multitude: Sabine Bitter and Helmet Weber, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Multitude: Sharon Ya'ari, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Multitude: Sun-Hee Choi, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Multitude: Taiji Matsue, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Multitude: Txuspo Poyo, September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Sarah Dobai [1 of 2], September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Sarah Dobai [2 of 2], September 5, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Blue Diamond '68: Architecture and Design Project Series [1 of 2], November 7, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Blue Diamond '68: Architecture and Design Project Series [2 of 2], November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Painting as Paradox: Administrative, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Painting as Paradox: Administrative, Financial, Shipping, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Painting as Paradox: Andrea P. DeFlorio, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Painting as Paradox: Anton Vidokle, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Painting as Paradox: Artists' Slides, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Painting as Paradox: Augusto Arbizo, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Painting as Paradox: Barnaby Fumas, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Painting as Paradox: Benjamin Edwards, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Painting as Paradox: Blake Rayne, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Painting as Paradox: Brad Hampton, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Painting as Paradox: Brenda Zlamany, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Painting as Paradox: Carl Eckhoff, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Painting as Paradox: Carla Klein, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Painting as Paradox: Carolyn Carr, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Painting as Paradox: Carrie Yamaoka, November 7, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Painting as Paradox: Catalogue, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Painting as Paradox: Claire Corey, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Painting as Paradox: Darren Wardle, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Painting as Paradox: David Nicholson, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Painting as Paradox: Delivery Receipts, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Painting as Paradox: Dorota Kolodziejczyk, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Painting as Paradox: Elizabeth Conlon, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Painting as Paradox: Ellen Altfest, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Painting as Paradox: Ellen Harvey, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Painting as Paradox: E. Mary Doherty, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Painting as Paradox: Evan Lintermans, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Painting as Paradox: Frantiska and Tim Gilman, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Painting as Paradox: Gabriela Schutz, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Painting as Paradox: Graham Parks, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Painting as Paradox: Gyoko Yoshida, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Painting as Paradox: Inaki Gracenea, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Painting as Paradox: Isca Greenfield-Sanders, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Painting as Paradox: James Sheehan, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Painting as Paradox: Jan Baracz, November 7, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Painting as Paradox: Jane Callister, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Painting as Paradox: Janice Handleman, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Painting as Paradox: Jay Davis, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Painting as Paradox: Jessica Rohrer, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Painting as Paradox: Jose Leon Cerrillo, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Painting as Paradox: Judith Eisler, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Painting as Paradox: Julie Mehretu, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Painting as Paradox: Karel Funk, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Painting as Paradox: Karlos Carcamo, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Painting as Paradox: Kehinde Wiley, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Painting as Paradox: Kelley Walker, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Painting as Paradox: Kieran Kinney, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Painting as Paradox: Leon Golub, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Painting as Paradox: Loan Form Agreements, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Painting as Paradox: Mara Korkola, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Painting as Paradox: Marc Handleman, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Painting as Paradox: Maria Cruz, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Painting as Paradox: Mark Bradford, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Painting as Paradox: Mark Orange, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Painting as Paradox: Matt Chomsky, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Painting as Paradox: Matthew Ritchie, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Painting as Paradox: Matthew Strauss, November 7, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Painting as Paradox: Michael Gibson, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Painting as Paradox: Michael Phelan, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Painting as Paradox: Millree Hughes, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Painting as Paradox: Minako Iwamura (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Painting as Paradox: Monica Bradley, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Painting as Paradox: Nathaniel Quinn, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Painting as Paradox: Nayda Collazo-Llorens, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Painting as Paradox: Odili Donald Odita, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Painting as Paradox: Perry Hall, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Painting as Paradox: Promotional, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Painting as Paradox: Research [1 of 2], 2002 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Painting as Paradox: Research [2 of 2], 2002 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Painting as Paradox: Rihard Pasquarelli, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Painting as Paradox: Roberto Bermejo, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Painting as Paradox: Sebastian Blanck, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Painting as Paradox: Seth Price, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Painting as Paradox: Simon Aldridge, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Painting as Paradox: Sunny Kim, November 7, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Painting as Paradox: Sze Tsung Leong, November 7, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Painting as Paradox: Terry Haggerty, November 7, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Painting as Paradox: Thomas Pihl, November 7, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Painting as Paradox: Tim Doud, November 7, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Painting as Paradox: Valentina Loi, November 7, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Body and the Archive: Administrative, Financial, Loan Forms, January 13, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Body and the Archive: Administrative, Financial, Shipping, January 18, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Body and the Archive: Artists' Files, January 18, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Body and the Archive: Artists' Files, January 18, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Body and the Archive: Artists' Files, January 18, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Body and the Archive: Artists' Files, January 18, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Body and the Archive: Performance Administrative, Research, January 13, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Body and the Archive: Readings, January 18, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Body and the Archive: Readings, January 18, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Film Tombs: Lynn Cazabon, January 18, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Getting to Know the Stranger (Photographs by Other People): David Coggins, January 18, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Video from Sidi El Asphalt's Moulid: Wael Shawky, January 18, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Main Space = Project Spaces: Administrative, March 8, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Main Space = Project Spaces: Artists' Files, Promotional, March 8, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Administrative, June 4, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Administrative, Promotional, June 4, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Administrative, Christine Messineo, June 4, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Financial, Promotional, June 4, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Promotional [1 of 2], June 4, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Promotional [2 of 2], June 4, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Zaha Hadid - Shipping, June 4, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Abstruction: Administrative, Promotional - Jessica Bronson, Yunhee Min, Jessica Rankin, Lisa Sigal, September 6, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Abstruction: Artists' Files, September 6, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Abstruction: Artists' Files, September 6, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Sign as Surface - Administrative, Financial, Promotional, September 6, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Installation, Shipping, September 6, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Sign as Surface - Labels, September 6, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Sign as Surface - Peter Zellner Administrative File [1 of 2], September 6, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Sign as Surface - Peter Zellner Administrative File [2 of 2], September 6, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Morir ('til Death): Miguel Angel Rios, September 6, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Visual Aids: Share Your Vision, October 22, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Superstudio - Life Without Objects, November 20, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Malevich Museum Biberach: Albretch Schafer, Katsuhiro Saiki, November 20, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Adam Putnam: Magic Lanterns, January 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - AnTe Liu: Tackiness and Anti-Power, January 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - William Pope.L: eRacism - Administrative, January 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - William Pope.L: eRacism - Installation Notebook, January 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - William Pope.L: eRacism - Promotional, January 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Hitoshi Abe, March 2003 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Kaye Donachie: Never Learn Not to Love, March 1, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: L.E.F.T. - Souatville - Franchising the Domestic, March 9, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Establishing Shot, March 9, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Robin Rhode: Untitled (the Score), May 14, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Can You Feel It, Repeat Performance, R.U.R.: Marie Jager, May 20, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Salad Days: Administrative, July 15, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Salad Days: Administrative, July 15, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Salad Days: Artist Files, July 15, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Flux Room - Reiser and Umemoto, September 14, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Based on a True Story, Followed Home: Megan McGinnis, September 14, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Night of 1000 Drawings: Announcements, Agreements, November 3, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Drawing Show - Studio Visits [1 of 2], 2002, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Drawing Show - Studio Visits [2 of 2], 2002, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - November - December Project Space Financial, November 2004 - January 2005 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Open Video Call Program, December 2004 - January 2005 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Sensual Hyper Tension, November 12, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Flipside, November 12, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Swetlana Heger, January 18, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Log Cabin: Administrative, January 18, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Log Cabin: Administrative, January 18, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Log Cabin: Administrative, Loan Agree Forms, January 18, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Log Cabin: Loan Agreement Forms, January 18, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Sari Carel: Champs Elysees, March 9, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Model Modernisms, March 9, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Model Modernisms, March 9, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Model Modernisms: Carol Bove Theft, March 19, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Bard College's Center for Curatorial Studies: Four by Four, Things Fall Apart All Over Again, May 7, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Kuo: You Are the Everything and Everything Is In You, June 21, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Heidrun Holzfeind: Exposed, June 21, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Hunch and Flail, June 21, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - But It Was All Geen: Ryan Gander, September 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - International Geographic: Rafael Ormella, Kelly Poe, September 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Wild Walls New York - A Sense of Films in/on Architecture, October 6, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Administrative, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Administrative, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Administrative, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Fatima Hoang - ...bowl like no one is watching, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Kevin McCarty - Chameleon Club, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Empty Space With Exciting Events: Promotional, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Empty Space: Quisquieya Henriguez - Intertextualidad, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Empty Space: Robert Arndt - Lines for the Next Exhibition, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Empty Space: Sabrina Gschwandtner, November 16, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Administrative, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Carl James Ferrero, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Catherine Ross, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Chad Nelson, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Diane Derr, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: James Kennedy, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Ra di Martino, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Sara Greenberger, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - The Mind/Body Problem: Vera Iliatova, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Mountains and Constellations: Karen Gunderson, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Simply Because You're Near Me: Jennie C. Jones, January 12, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Architecture and Design Project Series: Baskets, March 8, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - When Artists Say We: Administrative, March 8, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - When Artists Say We: Administrative, March 8, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - When Artists Say We: Administrative, March 8, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Emerging Curators Series: Daniel Joglar-Cosas Sin Hacer, Cosas Para Hacer Manana, May 16, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Emerging Curator Series: Jakup Ferri - An Artist Who Does Not Speak English Is No Artist, May 16, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 2)